If you sell
products or services
to apartment buildings,
you know that
getting in early
matters because that
client becomes sticky.
So that's why
I look for
signals for early
development,
looking for permits,
looking for construction,
right?
And that got
easier with me
using CraneSignal.
CraneSignal allows me
to find the
leads early for
very big and
small apartment buildings.
Now when I
go here,
I'm able to
actually ask their
agent for what
the best leads
for them right
now.
I sell software
to these apartments,
and so I
asked them for
the best leads
to sell the
software right now.
It gave me
the number,
it gave me
where it's at,
and everything I
needed to know.
And I also
get to download
the actual PDF,
which is amazing.
For free.
I didn't even
sign in.
So I would
say definitely use
CraneSignal if you
need more leads.